getthebet.com 2012-09-12

# getthebet.com Any Time Any Game Any Wager

**PRIVACY POLICY**

GoTo Entertainment and its family of sites believe in committing to strong business practices. First and foremost we are committed to you and your privacy. GoTo Entertainment has created this Privacy Statement for its websites. 

Des Sports Informatiques strives to ensure that it provides an accountable and secure gaming and banking experience. 

Our Customer can be confident that in playing on this site your personal details and financial information are kept private and are not misused. 

We are proud of our reputation for fair play and our technology ensuring the secure transfer of funds. GoTo Entertainment uses various processors for all financial transactions.  The information relating to each transaction is protected by our unique encryption system.  For more information on this visit our Secure Banking section on our website. 

Your account and up to date financial information relating to your account is assured as GoTo Entertainment records of all your transactions.  We provide you with a fully transparent comprehensive audit trail on all games you play detailing the sums wagered, won or lost.  We believe that this will give you absolute confidence in all your dealings with GoTo Entertainment 

GoTo Entertainment respect your choice to play our games are wish to ensure your total privacy.  We guarantee that access to your information is restricted to you by your unique user name and password.  Your customer details are stored and managed under the strictest supervision.  We adhere to the stringent tests set out by the Data Protection Agency in England , verified by Thawte to ensure your peace of mind. 

For further information on how GoTo Entertainment uses, protects and stores information we receive from our site visitors and our customers do not hesitate to contact our Technical team by sending an email to [CS@BetGoTo.com ](mailto:CS@BetGoTo.com). 

GoTo Entertainment believes that good business relationships are built over time by way of honesty and trust. That is why the privacy of your information is extremely important for us and to our members. Simply put, we are committed to protecting your privacy so that your experience with GoTo Entertainment is a pleasant and secure one. 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of any information you give us. Through state of the art equipment and strict in-house polices you and your personal information will always be safe and secure. 

Our policy at GoTo Entertainment is that all personal information you provide, such as your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, and credit card number, is private and confidential. Your personal information is stored in a secure location and is accessible only by designated staff. All information is for internal purposes only, including the information our web site tracks concerning visits. While we compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our site, this information is used only to help better serve our members. 

We operate using IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your wagering account. 

GoTo Entertainment also logs IP addresses for system administration purposes. IP addresses are logged to track a user's session. This gives us an idea what parts of our site users are visiting. We do not link IP address to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will remain anonymous. However in cases of suspected fraud, it is possible for our system developers to review these log files and correlate them with individual player accounts and thereby establish with a high degree of certainty what happened and who was involved. 

Each e-mail will give you specific instructions about how to remove your name from our mailing list. If you wish to stop receiving our promotional e-mails, simply follow the instructions at the bottom of each e-mail. 

Our online surveys, emails, and contests ask visitors for contact information such as name, email address, and other miscellaneous details. The information and statistics we receive are used solely to provide better service to our customers. It will not be shared, rented, sold, or distributed in any manner to any other person, company, or organization. 

This site contains links to other sites. GoTo Entertainment is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

In return for this guarantee of privacy, we ask that customers are ready to provide security information in all correspondence with GoTo Entertainment and that this information is kept completely confidential at all times. This includes customer's account ID and password. We also reserve the right to request proof of identification. 

GoTo Entertainment will also want to offer promotions to clients who use the web site. To assure the quality of client communications, GoTo Entertainment provides clients with the opportunity to "opt-in" to weekly newsletters. However, there is a certain minimum level of communication needed for a client to play effectively with GoTo Entertainment so everyone with an account will get some notices and promotional emails. 

If a client needs to change their address, email address and/or telephone number, they should submit their changes directly from the GoTo Entertainment web site (under Our INFO CENTER/Contact Us" or by calling 1-888-333-PLAY (7529)). New information will be verified with card-issuing banks and updated accordingly. Clients must ensure that card-issuing banks have their new address and phone number PRIOR to submitting their Profile Updates. 

A client who loses their account login information may retrieve it via "Forgot My Log-in Info," found on the login screens of the GoTo Entertainment web site, or by clicking on the relevant FAQ in the Help section. All changes made to account holder information, whether done on-line or by telephone, are logged. It is our policy not to change an account holder's name unless we have an official name change notification on file (e.g. marriage certificate, notice of name change). 

We are strongly opposed to internet Spam. We DO NOT Spam. The only emails sent are to registered members of GoTo Entertainment or its family of sites. We will occasionally send mailers via third party affiliates, however ONLY if those affiliates have asked their client base to OPT IN and receive third party email. 

For any other questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealing with the web site, you can contact us between 8 AM and 12 AM ET, seven days a week using any of the following methods: 

**1-888-333-PLAY (7529)**  

You can also reach us via postal mail at: 

Customer Service Department.   
GoTo Entertainment   
Interlink #542   
PO Box 02-5635   
Miami , FL 33102
